Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records Concerning Admissions and Registration
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Architecture, Yale University, records concerning admissions and registration
1951-2006
RU 1012
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
47
The records consist of admission and registration records, correspondence, course schedules and syllabi, programs, and press clippings documenting various activities of the Yale School of Architecture related to student administration and support. Also included are records documenting the 1963 dedication of the School of Architecture building.
Yale University. School of Architecture
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 19-E (YRG 19-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Architecture.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Architecture, 2006-2009.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of admission and registration records, correspondence, course schedules and syllabi, programs, and press clippings documenting various activities of the Yale School of Architecture related to student administration and support. Also included are records documenting the 1963 dedication of the School of Architecture building.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Architecture -- Study and teaching; Schools of architecture; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Admission; Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Admission; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University. School of Architecture
- Admissions and registration records, 1951-2005; Accession 2007-A-028
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
  - Grade sheets, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 12)
  - Spring midterm warnings, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Grade sheets, 1994 -2002 (Box 2, Folder 14 - 35)
  - Prior faculty lists, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Course evaluation procedures and corrections, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fall registration packet, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Fall course enrollment, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Spring course enrollment, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Fall courses, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Faculty class lists - Fall, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Fall class lists, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Spring course enrollment, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Spring class lists, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Spring course enrollment, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Fall class lists, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Fall enrollment count, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Fall course verifications, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Fall class lists, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Spring course verifications, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Spring verifications, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Course enrollments, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fall course lists, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Fall verifications, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Class enrollment, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Course enrollments, 1989-1997 (Box 3, Folder 56 - 64)
  - Course enrollment counts, 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Spring waivers, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Fall waivers, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Spring waivers, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fall waivers, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fall waivers, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Fall waivers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Spring waivers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Waivers, 1990-1997 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Student Records, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Grade List, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Lottery, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Syllabi, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Verifications, miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 79 - 80)
  - Spring course registration, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 81 - 83)
  - Fall library course, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Fall course schedule, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Spring course schedule, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 86 - 89)
  - Spring studios, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Fall course schedule, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 91 - 92)
  - Courses, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Fall sample registration packet, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Spring required courses, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Spring electives, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Spring course schedule, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Spring student schedules, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Spring course registration, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Fall student course schedule, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Summer course registration, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Spring course schedule, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Spring schedule changes, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Fall course registration, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Spring final course schedules, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Spring enrollment counts, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Fall course registration, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Fall course schedule, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Fall verification lists, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Fall course registration, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Course descriptions, Spring, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Course syllabi, etc., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Course syllabi, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Course syllabi, etc., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Course information, 1990-1999, 2003, undated (Box 6, Folder 114 - 125)
  - Face Book, 1993-2004 (Box 6, Folder 126 - 136)
  - Bulletin - prior college information, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Bulletins, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 138 - 140)
  - Bulletin distribution, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Orientation, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 142 - 145)
  - Fall registration, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Orientation registration, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Admission Reports, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Billing, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Loan deferrals, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 150 - 153)
  - Loan deferrals - Clearing House, 1993-2001 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Degree requirement tracking, undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Degree verification, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Miscellaneous course information, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Distribution requirements, 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 158 - 161)
  - Joint degree information, 1993-1999 (Box 6, Folder 162 - 164)
  - Commencement information, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 165 - 168)
  - Graduation, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Licensure for architects, AIA Connecticut, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Holds, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Diploma list, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Graduation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Building, 1958-1963 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Graduation, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 176 - 178)
  - Directions to graduating students, A and A program, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Graduation, 1959-1966, 1997/1998 (Box 7, Folder 180 - 188)
  - Graduation, 1951-1958 (Box 8, Folder 189 - 196)
  - Educational policy and admissions, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Building Fund, 1959-1965 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Housing, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Job opportunities, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Job opportunities (requests and recommendations), 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Job opportunities A - K, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Library, 1950-1956 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - History of Art, 1951-1957 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Application Statistics, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Dedication materials, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 206 - 208)
  - Dedication dinners, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Dedication Day expenses, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Dedication Day program, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Commencement programs, 1959-1970 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Statistics - financial aid, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Statistics - course enrollments, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Statistical Reports, 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 215 - 219)
  - Institutional research, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 220 - 222)
  - Hegis report, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Institutional research statistics, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Wintergreen Orchard House graduate survey for College Edge, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Open house, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Independent studio proposal form; rules of lottery, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 227)
  - Studio Descriptions, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 228 - 229)
  - Advanced studio descriptions; new course descriptions/syllabi, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Graphics summer course; bookcase project; Rome, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Course registration (lottery), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - Schedule, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 233 - 234)
  - Schedules; syllabi; course class lists, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Rules (and Curriculum) Committee, 1985, 1989, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Student Elections, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - Website for School of Architecture, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - International Center English courses, etc., 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Admission reply cards, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Admission miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Admissions, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 242 - 244)
  - Open house-spring, 1999-2004 (Box 9, Folder 245 - 253)
  - Open house-fall, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 254 - 255)
  - Open house information, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Admissions program, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 257)
  - Admissions, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 258)
  - Miscellaneous: banner, admissions, computer program, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 259)
  - Open house-fall, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Fall open house advisement meetings, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Open house poster - fall, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Open house - fall, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 263 - 264)
  - Open house poster - fall, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 265)
  - Open house - fall, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 266 - 267)
  - Fall open house agenda and logistics, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Open house - administrative, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Summer mailing, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 270)
  - July mailing
    - 1st year M.Arch. II, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - Trading letters, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - Samples; originals, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - 1st year M.Arch. I, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Returning students, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - 1st year MED, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - Student addresses, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Originals, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - 1st year M.Arch. I, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - 1st year M.Arch. II, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - 1st year MED student, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 281)
    - Returning students, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - Extras, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 283)
    - Mailing, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - New M.Arch. II, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - New MED, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - All returning, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Advanced M.Arch I, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - New M.Arch I, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 289)
  - May mailing, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 290 - 293)
  - General mailing, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 294)
  - Statistics
    - OIR, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 295 - 299)
    - Applicant tally, 1999-2005 (Box 10, Folder 300)
    - Profiles 2000-2002, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 301)
    - Admission statistics, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 302)
    - Admissions, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 303)
    - Student roster, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 304)
    - Miscellaneous memos, signs, etc., 2001 (Box 10, Folder 305)
    - Admitted students, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 306)
    - OIR, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 307)
    - Admissions, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 308)
    - OIR, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - OIR admissions, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 310)
    - Enrollments, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 311)
    - Statistics, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, etc., 2001 (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - Comparative tuition and fees-- Architecture, 1986-1997, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Student rosters and statistics, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Admissions
    - Student lists, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - Lists; letters, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - Conditional admits, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 318)
    - M.Arch. I, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 319)
    - Bulletin information, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 320)
    - GRE, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 321)
    - Web information, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 322)
    - Decisions, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 323)
    - Letters - tracking, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 324)
    - Decision letters, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 325)
    - All applicants, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 326)
    - Admission - fall, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 327)
    - Admission committee, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 328)
    - Ratings, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 329)
    - Conditional admits, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 330)
    - Letters, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 331)
    - Tracking letters, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 332)
    - Responses, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 333)
    - OISS orientation for new international students, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 334)
    - Decisions, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 335)
    - Admitted applicants, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 336)
    - Portfolio return, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 337)
    - List of applicants, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 338)
    - M.Arch. II admissions, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 339)
    - M.Arch. I admissions, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 340)
    - Conditional admits, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - Reports/Banner, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 342)
    - Portfolio return, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 343)
    - Missing items, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 344)
    - Data entry, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 345)
    - Admitted - O.H., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 346)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 347)
    - Letters, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 348)
  - Institute of International Education/Fulbright Information, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 349)
  - Asian Relief Rules, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 350)
  - Bursar Billing Request, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 351)
  - Cumulative Debt Survey, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 352)
- Admissions and registration records, 1998-2005; Accession 2008-A-192
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - July Mailing Information File, 2004 July (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - May Mailing Information, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - May Returning Students Mailing Information, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - May Mailing Information File, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Open House File, -2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Open House Invitation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Open House Flyer, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Admissions Information - Letters and et al, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
  - Admissions Decisions, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Conditional Admit Lists, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - M.Arch I, MED, and M.Arch II, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14-19)
  - Emails/housing/public, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dean's and Chair's Sample Letters, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - First Round Cuts Lists, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Accepted students, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Reviewed Applicants, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Response cards, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Open House Information, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Open House Registration Forms, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - YOSA Open House, 2003 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Open House Advisement Forms, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pre-Registration Forms A-L, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Pre-Registration Forms M-Z, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Open House Stats, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Admissions and registration records, 1990-2006; Accession 2009-A-188
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2082
  - Student Rosters: Lists, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - Summer Registration: Correspondence, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bulletin Changes: Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Outside Students: Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic Calendar Information: Calendar, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Curriculum Committee: Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16-19)
  - Faculty Committees and Student Representatives: Lists, 1985-2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Faculty List: Lists, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Meeting Notes: Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - Registration: Correspondence, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Registration: Correspondence, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Waivers: Lists, 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Waivers: Lists, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Registration: Lists, 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Domestic Partners: Letter, 2004 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Course Schedules M.Arch I: Lists, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31-33)
  - Registration: Lists, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Course Schedules: Lists, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Undergrad Course Schedule: Lists, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sample Folder for Open House: Sample, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Grade Lists: Lists, 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Grade Lists: Lists, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Grade Emails: Correspondence, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Grade Lists: Grade Lists, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Student Evaluations: Lists, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Studio Evaluations, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Academic Course Evaluations, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Student Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Course Schedules M.Arch I, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
  - Course Schedules MED, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48-49)
  - Courses, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Students' Schedules, 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Course Schedules, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Verified Class Lists, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Approved Class Lists from Faculty, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Class Lists, 2004 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Late Registration Fee charges, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Applicant Tally: Lists, 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Applicant Tally: Lists, 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Applicant Tally: Lists, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Course Evaluations: Lists, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Grades: Lists, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Grade Lists with Course and Student Evals: Lists, 0 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Open House: Lists, Spring 2004 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Summer Rome Seminar: Lists, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 64-68)
  - Open House On-Line Register: Lists, 2005 Spring (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Open House: Lists, 2005 Spring (Box 2, Folder 70-71)
  - Sample Folder Yale: Lists, 2004 Fall (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Open House Advisements Comments: Comments, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 73-74)
  - Open House: Schedule and Assorted Lists, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Open House: Registration Forms, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Open House: Advisement Appointments, 2004 Fall (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Open House-No Shows: Registration Forms, 2004 Fall (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Open House: Poster, 2004 Fall (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Admissions Committee General: Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Applicant Tally: Lists, 2000 Fall (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Portfolio Returns: Lists, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Open House: Lists, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Open House: Completed Worksheets, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Open House Notes and Info: Notes, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Open House: Schedule and Assorted Lists, 2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Open House On-Line: Registration Forms, 2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Open House Registrations: Attendees List, 2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Summer Registration: Lists, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Faculty List: Lists, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Fall Academic Warnings: Correspondence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Academic Warning: Correspondence, Spring 2003 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Registration: Correspondence, Spring 2003 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Class Lists: Correspondence, Spring 2003 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Course Enrollment List: Lists, Spring 2003 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Course Enrollment: Lists, Fall 2003 (Box 2, Folder 96)